clearfxsignals.com 2018-08-28

# Privacy – Clear FX Signals

**ClearFXSignals.com Privacy Policy**

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**  
What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To process transactions

Upon purchasing you will be asked for information pertaining to payment processing. We do not collect any of that information but rather we use Secure Credit Card Processing via the ClickBank Secure Payment Gateway – one of the largest, most respected and secure merchant credit card service companies in the world.

To send periodic emails

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. and offers for third party trading and forex related products that we will notify you about. You can instantly unsubscribe from our mailing list at any time.

**How do we protect your information?**

All transactions are handled by Clickbank.com.  We do not process any payment transactions.  When you place an order you are taken off of our site to Clickbank’s system.  You can view their privacy policy at <http://www.clickbank.com/privacy.html>

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.)  are not collected by us or stored on our servers.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

While we maintain ownership of the ClearFXSignals.com website and domain we do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you.  If necessary we may also release your information to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.  In the event that we sell the ClearFXSignals.com website and domain we may also sell our customer list, which would consist of only First names and Email addresses but no other information.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not aim to collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.ClearFXSignals.com/terms

**  
****Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**ClickBank is the retailer of this product.** CLICKBANK® is a registered trademark of Click Sales, Inc., a Delaware corporation located at 917 S. Lusk Street, Suite 200, Boise Idaho, 83706, USA and used by permission.  ClickBank’s role as retailer does not constitute an endorsement, approval or review of this product or any claim, statement or opinion used in promotion of this product.

Use the **BACK** button on your browser to return to the previous page
